eforcity.com 2017-10-08

# Privacy Policy

eForCity Corporation has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our company’s commitment to privacy. The privacy of our customers is one of our top priorities and the information we collect is completely confidential. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: eForCity.com. 

**The Information We Collect**

We collect your information when you place an order, abandon your shopping cart or sign up for our email newsletter. Information we collect in these instances includes your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit or debit card information. 

**The Way We Use Your Information**

We use the information you provided only to complete transactions, confirm orders and communicate shipping status. Your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or disclosed to any other parties other than for the purpose of processing your orders or delivering services requested by the customer. 

**Collection of Children’s Personal Information**

eForCity is committed to protecting the privacy and welfare of children. eForCity does not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. All products are sold for the purchase by adults only, if you are under the age of 18, you must seek approval from your parent or guardian to purchase products on this site. 

**Email Newsletter Opt-In/Opt Out**

If you subscribe to our email newsletter, we will use the email you provided to send company information and promotional materials only. Customers may choose to opt-out at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the email. 

**Do we Use Cookies and Why?**

eForCity uses cookies in order for us to customize certain Web pages to help identify you and your shopping cart. Cookies are small files sent and stored onto a user’s computer by our web browser. If you disabled the cookies for our website, we will be unable to recognize your browser and identify your shopping cart. 

We use your IP address to help administer our Web site and diagnose any problems with our server. Your IP address may also be used by a third part anonymously to gather broad demographic information for research purposes. Personally identifiable information will not be linked to IP addresses.

**Your Information Security**

We take [website security](https://www.websafeshield.com/) seriously, and have engaged WebSafe Shield to help us provide it. WebSafe Shield provides a service similar to [McAfee Secure](http://www.websafeshield.com/Compare-McAfee-Secure.html)'s daily scanning service, and we are notified as security vulnerabilities are descovered. WebSafe Shield is a leading and trusted security service that offers additional services ranging from [PCI Compliance](https://www.websafeshield.com/PCI-Compliance.html) to [Application Penetration Testing](http://www.websafeshield.com/application-penetration-testing.html). 

eForCity uses the Security for merchants from Yahoo! Services. Yahoo! uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption while transmitting certain kinds of information, such as financial services information or payment information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed at the bottom of most browser windows during SSL transactions that involve credit cards and other forms of payment. Credit card numbers are SSL encrypted whenever Yahoo! requests it for payment or verification purposes. Customer information will be stored securely on our servers. Once customers choose to store or enter a credit card number on Yahoo!, it will not be displayed in its entirety when customers retrieve or edit it in the future. Instead of the entire number, customers will only see asterisks and either the first four digits or the last four digits of the number.

For information about Yahoo store Security see [Security at Yahoo!](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/security/). 

**Our Commitment to You**

eForCity does not sell, trade, or transfer any of our customer’s personally identifiable information to outside parties. Personal information will not be used beyond what is necessary to assist your purchases and services you have requested. If, at any point, trusted third parties are needed to assist our web site or in servicing you, they must agree to keep this information confidential. eForCity also reserves the right to release your personally identifiable information when required by law enforcement or in order to protect our or other’s rights, safety, or property.

**Amendment of Privacy Policy**

eForCity reserves the right to change our privacy policy and will post those changes on this page, our homepage, and other places we deem appropriate. You will be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances will information be disclosed. Please review our Privacy & Security page frequently for any changes.

This policy was last modified on 14/06/2010

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact:

18525 Railroad St.

City of Industry, CA 91748

United States

626.442.3168
